Hello everyone, we are Not Ecole Me.
Soon we, Not Ecole Me, will be,
We will be celebrating our 5th anniversary,
We would like to do an outrodon using the songs that we have participated in the past 5 years,
We would like to do an outrodon using songs that we have participated in over the past 5 years.
Outrodon!
It's an outrodon!
It's not intro-don, is it?
We have prepared 15 songs in total,
The person who can answer the most questions will be the winner.
The songs that are eligible are all the songs that Noimy has participated in up to now.
Some are unit songs and some are solo songs.
If you know the correct answer, there is a ping pong table in front of you.
There is a ping pong table in front of you.
It's a little far away,
Don't fall down.
Safety is important.
Noimy often falls, so have fun and be safe.
Let's do our best!
I'll do my best!
Okay, first question, please!
Pipe down!
Is this it?
Is this your center?
Good luck.
Yes, sir!
You're late.
Are you... are you Pipel?
I want to hear it one more time.
You like that?
From the National Guard.
Wow.
Bye-bye.
eeehhhhhhh tel
galaxy
me
And anha
sneeze
What?
I'm in.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
The Meat Box Song.
Oh, no, no, no.
Let's hear it again.
So coordinate haha
erotic
I've got a possible...
I'm
moisture
This is
Hikaru
me
Yay!
Teasing game
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It's a day off.
A day break from my thoughts.
Wait.
Good night.
Oh, wait.
Revolutionary March.
No, no, no.
Come on.
Mood Thunder
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
You did good.
Not even close.
What?
What about this one?
Uhhh...
At first.
Ehhhh...
Yay.
Sorry, wait.
It's not good.
Let's hurry up and move on.
5th question, please.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha, I'm so sorry.
ahahahahahaha
Buber bas
Save why
f im too n gatcher
Aaaaah no!
What?
No, it's not.
El Tri Galiakiris?
No, no.
No.
Go ahead.
Marshmallow rot.
Wow.
Oh, calm down.
Oh, man.
Gaat for the bangs.
you should go by the name of your construction company
Why?
Question 7, please.
I don't know anymore.
your daybreak.
booboo!
Junk fist
Add oil
p Boeing
Kula Japona
tearing
Yes with a little view
I've heard of it.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Oh! Okay, okay! One more time.
Oh, no.
Well, I haven't answered your question yet, so I'm going to go.
Oh, Selnick?
Surprising.
But you look like him.
Oh!
The Eutectic Program.
AH!!!
ASSOLUTELAY!!!
Such İş!
There are things you don't know about Japan
5th question
What's this?
Can I? Ready?
Did anybody get it?
I got it! I got it!
I don't know, I don't know, I know.
For three?
Let's all cry.
It's zero.
Are you sure?
Here we go.
Tritornets.
Yay!
I'm so excited.
Second one.
Eighth question, please.
What was that?
What the hell was that?
What? What? What?
Oh, no! One more time, please!
Huh. **
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'll атов you.
What is this
jajan
all you can say
eh?
Eh, this is different, I think
Uh, what?
I wonder if she's buying it.
What? Am I buying?
What?
Hey, viver.
Oh!
Mahalo for risking.
Oh, my God.
Wow, it's so strong!
What?
No, icides.
Oh, no!
I don't know about that.
Can we have the fourth question, please?
Fabe.
This one's for you.
What a sheep!
What?
Reykiss.
Yay!
Second one.
Two...
Listen up, everyone.
This is question 10.
The 10th question, please.
What?
That's where we all lose confidence.
You lose confidence, don't you?
I'm in.
What?
It's a cheerful song.
I'm sure it is.
Majol
Mint
No, it's not.
I don't think so.
Grandma.
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God.
There we go. There we go.
Oh, man.
I got a six.
How are you feeling?
Just get me a chair right there.
I'll just be a minute.
I'll get the three of us.
Next, please.
Oh, no.
kitten tone
Booper.
ana
Okay, okay, okay! I got it! I got it! I got it! I got it!
What? You got it?
I feel like I should be the one to answer that.
Hey.
I get it.
I mean, what's there to look at?
Uhhh...
Oh, my God! That's great!
Well, good night.
Excuse me.
What? What's the point?
Well, let's just keep going, shall we?
Okay, I'm coming.
Squeeze!
Whoo-hoo!
What? A little...
Ayumi.
Yume-chan said
Cranes are flowers.
Huh?
Which way did I start?
Aoi...
Wow.
Aoi. Yu, the soy sauce guy.
Soy sauce.
Oh, wow.
Oh, oh, you can listen to me now.
Aoi, please.
Okay, one more time.
Let's go a little longer.
Okay.
Oh, hey.
Is it the brothers' song, by the way?
Wrong.
Wait, isn't this it?
That's the moment to start teasing.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What?
What? It's me.
What? What?
You're such a tease!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What?
I love you so much!
Secret Park
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, man, I'm the only one who gets it.
I'll go take a look.
I don't know. I don't think so.
Our Imaju.
Ha-ha-ha.
What?
Huh? No?
We'll just rub it in like this.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Huh?
Did you just say "imaje"?
Yes, I did. I was wrong.
But it's the same thing in emo-century.
You totally said it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I thought about it. Now I'm thinking about it, and I'm going away.
Send me home, please!
Laughing.
That's what I'm talking about.
Look at me.
I don't know.
Who is it?
Is that everyone's original song?
We're all gonna get out of here.
Oh, no?
Okay, okay.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Does everyone really mean...
Does that mean everyone?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What should we talk about next time we see each other?
Wait! Oh, my God! It's really everyone!
Really!
That boom at the end.
That was amazing! We don't have much time left.
Let's focus!
Please!
Piano sound.
What? You?
What? Maybe?
Maybe!
Amber flowers?
Oh, my God!
I'm an amber flower today!
I was so nervous you were going to guess.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
They said it's the last one.
Rust?
Oh!
What's your score, Miru?
I'm at about a seven.
Seven.
That's right.
Eight.
An eight.
Well, I'd like to give you a 10.
Okay.
A hundred?
All right.
You really want to get 100?
A thousand.
I'm up 1,000 points.
Let's do it.
Last one.
Please do it.
Kaua-peo as...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
aname
Yes, sir.
Pow!
I hear a sizzling sound.
Yes, yes, yes.
That was your sound.
Yay.
Wow.
That was your sound.
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow!
Aaaaah! It was your sound!
Okay, so, let's see, Mirei gets one point!
And Nacchan gets 2 points!
I got 3 points!
And, Miruten got 1008 points!
Yay!
Yay! Thank you so much!
Isn't it amazing? I was really impressed.
I think it boosted your confidence. But I'm happy for you.
That's all for now.
I'll be back next month with another 5th anniversary project,
Please subscribe to our channel!
And on February 24th, the day the group was formed,
Furu-san and Iko no Ijou channel!
We will be holding a live broadcast to commemorate the 5th anniversary of the formation of Not Equal Me!
Please come and watch!
That's all for now!
Bye bye!